Guide to the Marjorie Perloff Papers M1504
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Invitations to Give Papers/Conference Materials
  - University of Nevada, Las Vegas, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - University of Copenhagen 1998 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - ABRALIC 18-22 August 1998 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Yale University- The Whitney Humanities Center 1998 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - UC Riverside, Aesthetics and Difference: Cultural Diversity, Literature and the Arts, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - University of Missouri, St. Louis Center for International Studies, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Washington University in St. Louis 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art 1998 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - University of Kansas, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Pomona People, March 1999 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - UC San Diego 1999 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Barnard College, April 8-10, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - The People's Poetry Gathering April 9-11, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Watchman, Spy and Dead Man, Cologne/Frankfurt, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Bard College, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Emily Dickinson International Society Conference, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - The British Academy--Sarah Tryphena Phillips Lecture, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Sorbonne--Ezra Pound, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - University of London, Aesthetics Programme, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Invitations circa 2001-2003 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Princeton Fellowship 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Queen's University of Belfast, conferences 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - University of Michigan Institute for the Humanites, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Radio, Literature, and the Sound of Modernity 2003, Princeton (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - University of Texas at Austin, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Juniper Festival at University of Massachusetts, Amherst 2004 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - University of Washington, 2004: The Aura of Modernism (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Poetries of the 1940s, Orono, Maine, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Villa Aurora and Brazil, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Zukefsky and Jewish Conference 2004 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Belgium Documents (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Oklahoma (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Kelly Poets House (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Haroldo de Campos (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Beckett - Atlanta, Nov. 11-13 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Santa Cruz Readymade (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Johns Paper for Japan (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Rice U. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - LA County Museum of Art Docent Council 1999 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Poetry Society Panel March 15 1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - University of Notre Dame Conference 1998 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Jerusalem Conference 2000 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - National Poetry Foundation, University of Maine, Orono, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Transgressing Boundaries, Poster (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - School of the Arts Institute of Chicago, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - University of Miami: lecture (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Louisiana State University, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Bennington College 2000 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Washington University, February 2001, William Matheson Seminar (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - The Future of Form, University of Virginia, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - 1999-2000 Invitations (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Purdue University 1982 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - MLA at USC, Appointment (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Marxism, American Comparative Literature Association, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Materials on Biography (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Modern Language Review, Rethinking the Avant-Garde (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Forum on Periodization 1978 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Humanities Institute City University of New York (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - State University of New Jersey, Rutgers 1986 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Oppen Conference, UCSD, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Deus Ex Machina: Legacies of Futurism (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - IAUPE September '86 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Bar-Ilan University, Tel Aviv, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Radical Poetries, State University of NY, Buffalo 1988 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Japan June 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Australia and New Zealand September 1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - California Institute of Technology letter 1988 from Jeremy (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Hong Kong 5 December 1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo Paper: Artifice Once More (Notes) 1987 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - UCLA and USC and Catholic University of America 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - AWP in San Francisco, March 31-April 2 1988 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Yale University (1988) and the Poetry Project (1988) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - James Joyce and the Arts 1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Jean Cocteau Centenary Festival 1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Cage Talk--Strathmore, Washington Festival 1989 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - IAUPE August 1989 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - University of Louisville:20th Century Literature Conference, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - University of British Columbia 1989 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Brandeis University: American Comparative Literature Association 1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Invitations 1989--Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Vienna and Salzburg 1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Disciplining Literature, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Literature and Diversity--University of Alberta, Edmonton, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - University of Iowa, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - UCLA: The Disappearing Pheasant 2, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Honegger Conference, Catholic University, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Invitations 1994-1995 Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - MOCA Symposium on Duchamp, School Lecture, October 1995 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - University of New Hampshire: Assembling Alternatives, September 1996 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Modernism/Postmodernism City University of New York, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Invitations 1996--Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - PEN, The Korean Center, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Invitations 1996-1998, Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Patten Lectures, Indiana 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Invitation 1986-1997 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Invitations 1996-2005 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - 1995-2000 Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Penn Lecture October 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Indiana Conference on the Arts, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Individual Lectures 1974-1978 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Conferences 1977-1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Ethno-Poetics Conference, USC 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Claremont Conference on Modernism, 2-4 April 1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco Renaissance, February 9-12 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cage Symposium MOCA, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Beckett Conference - Correspondence, Austin, Texas 1984 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Pound Conference 1985 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Swarthmore 1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Pound Conference 1985 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Poetry Center, San Francisco - Poetry Panel 1984 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - World Literature Today Conference, 18-20 April 1985 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Hamburg August 1983 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Riverside Lecture February 10, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo: Radical Poetries, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Word and Image, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - ACLA 1994, Claremont Meeting (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Auburn University 1 October 1987 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Irvine (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Columbia Conference on Poetics (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Conferences 1986 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Kansas Postmodernism Panel, IAPL April 30-May 2 1987 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Oklahoma April 2-6 1987 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Anthropology of Change 1995 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Symposium of Work-in-Progress (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - IAUPE Copehagen 1995 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Montreal - June Engagements 1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Censorship and Silencing 1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - SFSU Review (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Cornell and Yale Conference Spring 1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Rejected Invitations Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Greg Ulmer University of Florida, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Berlin Info JFK 1990 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Joyce at Irvine Conference 1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Maine Program 1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Oregon Visit, Soundings 1991 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Milan-Poesia, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Cal State LA May 23, 1991 Kubal Lecture (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - World War I in Literature, Graz 1991 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - WCW Conference Rome 1991 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - UCSB Lecture 1991 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - ACLA San Diego - Comparative Literature Lecture 1991 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Poet's House April 22, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Maryland Paper--Bebe Pedrou Lecture 1992 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Notre Dame--Belmont 1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Talks--1990-1994 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Futurismo--UCLA 1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous--Montreal, Concordia Keynote 1992 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - UC Santa Cruz--Postmodernism 1992 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Notes and Xeroxes for Folger Essay (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Barnard Invitation (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Princeton--"New Urbanism" Conference, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Rolywholyover Circus MOCA 1993 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Romanticism/ Po Mo conference--Warwick Romanticism Conference 1991 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Passions Persons Powers April 30-May 3,1992 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - University of Washington 1991 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Cal Tech Primitivism Conference, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - India Lectures 1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - NYU Disappearing Pheasant (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Talk 1991 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - MLA Sessions: 89-92 Poetry Session (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - University of Kansas (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - UCLA Material Culture Conference (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Riverside (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Talk 1989 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Chicago/ Northwestern 1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Notre Dame 1989 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tikkun--Lectures/Conferences early 90s (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Naropa--July 7, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Avant-Garde and Difference: Russian Avant-Garde Conference 1990 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - AMS Panel 1990 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - University of Virginia and Queens University (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Poetry Festival: Fort Mason (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Yeats Lecture: Stanford Literary Lecture, October 10, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Beckett and War: University of Iowa French Conference, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Word and Image Folder (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Poets House, May 10 1990 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - ALA Paper June 2, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Series 5: Early Work
  - Master's Folder (including dissertation) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Yeats Book: Editorial Folder (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Yeats Book: Reviews Folder (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Lowell Book: Editorial Folder (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Lowell Book: Commentary (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Frank O'Hara Book: Editorial Folder (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - O'Hara Book: Publicity (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - O'Hara Book: Reviews (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - O'Hara Book: Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - O'Hara Book: Donald Allen Folder (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - O'Hara Book: Paperback Folder (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Series 6: The Futurist Moment/ 21st Century Modernism
  - Futurist Moment: Editorial Folder (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Futurist Moment: Advertisements (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Futurist Moment: Letters and Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Futurist Moment: Reviews (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Futurist Moment: Paperback Edition (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Futurist Moment: Portuguese Edition (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Futurist Moment: Second Edition (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Futurist Moment: Guggenheim Folder (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - 21st Century Modernism: Editorial Folder (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - 21st Century Modernism: Reviews Folder (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Series 7: Wittgenstein's Ladder/Radical Artifice
  - "R.A." - Editorial 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - "R.A." - Editorial 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - "R.A." - Permissions (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - "R.A." -Advertisements (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - "R.A." - Reviews (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - "R.A." - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - "W.L." - Editorial (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - "W.L." - Contract (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - "W.L." - Permissions (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - "W.L." - Promotions (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - "W.L." - Reviews (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - "W.L." - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Series 8: Poetry/Genre/John Cage
  - John Cage Book Reviews (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Cage book - editorial (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - John Cage week at Stanford (2002) (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Cage continuing studies course (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Cage book - correspondence (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Postmodern Genres - Editorial 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Postmodern Genres - Editorial 2 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Postmodern Genres - Reviews (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Poetry on and off the page (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Dance of the Intellect - miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Dance of the Intellect - correspondence (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Poetic License - Editorial (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Poetic License - Reviews (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Poetic License - Publicity (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Poetics of Indeterminacy - editorial (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Poetics of Indeterminacy - publicity (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Poetics of Indeterminacy - reviews (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Poetics of Indeterminacy - correspondence (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Series 9: Editorial Files
  - Critical Inquiry Folder - Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Journal Editor Correspondence Folder (2000-present) (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - University Press Correspondence (1965-1982) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Texas series - Poetry to Poetics (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sulfur Folder 2 - Jenny Penberthy (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sulfur Folder 1 - Eliot Weinberger (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Voices and Visions - WCW film (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Early Correspondence from Journals (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Library of America (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - PMLA advisory board (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous editorials (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Letters from Editors - articles (1976-1979) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Letters from Editors - books and journals (1986-1990) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Letters from Editors (1992-1995) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Letters from Journals - book inclusions (1997-2001) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Letters from Editors (1999-2002) (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Editorial Boards (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Consults on Books and Press Series (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Series 10: Miscellaneous
  - "Textual Practice" in honor of Perloff (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Awards, honors, general publicity (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Responses to review of Erica Jong (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Series 11: University Administration
  - Job Offers: CUNY 1988, Misc. from Dallas through 1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Job Offers: "Earlier Putative" (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Catholic University 1965-1970, appointment 1957 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - University of Maryland 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Irvine/Riverside Visiting Professorships 1984, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - USC and course evaluations (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University: appointment material, chair material (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University: Humanities Center Advisory Board (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Stanford University: Annual Report - course evaluations 1990-1994 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Series 12: Foundations/Centers/Fellowships Applications, Advising, and Consults
  - Miscellaneous Foundations, Grants, etc. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Center for Behavioral Studies (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Academy of Literary Studies (defunct.) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Radcliffe Institute (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - 2nd Guggenheim Fellowship Application (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship Application 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities 1985 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - American Comparative Literature Association 1995 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Triennial Council (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Tour 1995 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship Consults (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - MacArthur Foundation (Box 38, Folder 12)